[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ruby slippers Dorothy wears in the film The Wizard of Oz were actually encrusted with genuine rubies.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is an early computation device used in the 12th century by the Chinese.", "correct_answer": "Abacus", "incorrect_answers": ["Pascaline", "Napiers Bone", "Jacquards Loom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These fruits were used as wedding breakfast in France. Newlyweds had a soup of thinned sour cream, borage and powdered sugar, and these.", "correct_answer": "Strawberries", "incorrect_answers": ["Blackcurrant", "Cherries", "Peaches"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Amendment  to the US Constitution guarantees the right to privacy?", "correct_answer": "It is not guaranteed in the Constitution", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fourteenth", "The Fifteenth", "The Second"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This U.S. state was nicknamed Vacationland, and the nickname is used on license plates.", "correct_answer": "Maine", "incorrect_answers": ["Hawaii", "Nevada", "California"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Malaysian word pangolin mean?", "correct_answer": "Roll into a ball", "incorrect_answers": ["Armor", "Walking Pinecone", "Scaly Anteater"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dominica, New Zealand and Finland are three countries with high crime rates.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what field is the Golden Duck Award given annually?", "correct_answer": "Childrens science fiction", "incorrect_answers": ["Egocentric celebrities", "Politicians who waste government money", "Animated short films"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which British designer, son of Vivienne Westwood, founded the underwear label Agent Provocateur?", "correct_answer": "Joseph Corre", "incorrect_answers": ["John Rocha", "Christopher Bailey", "Alexander McQueen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This strange man-sized beast is thought to have been seen many times in the Point Pleasant area of West Virginia around the late 60s of the twentieth century.", "correct_answer": "Mothman", "incorrect_answers": ["Jabberwock", "Ghidorah", "Gorgon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is used as a cleansing remedy?", "correct_answer": "Crab Apple", "incorrect_answers": ["Cherry Plum", "Gentian", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is hottest?", "correct_answer": "a lightning bolt", "incorrect_answers": ["the surface of the sun", "the laser used in eye surgery", "a microwave oven"]}]